SUN CHEN

Address: 97 Belcher's St, Kennedy Town, Hong Kong

Email: Dragon.dev1994@gmail.com **Portfolio:** https://dreamoflife.netlify.app

Github: https://github.com/DarlingUUi

SUMMERY

I am a Full-Stack developer with 8+ years experiences in Web and Unity. I always pay my attention to the details of the projects and the clients. It improved quality of the project and relationship with the clients. Honesty and diligence are my strengths. Without these, I don't think about "SUCCESS". Also, flexible communication with the client help to decrease the period of the project.

EXPERIENCE

JAN 2020 - PRESENT

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, FREELANCER

- Developed Dapp using React / Redux / Redux-Saga / React Hooks / Web3, Ether.js and IPFS.
- Familiar with NFT projects such as NFT minting Dapp, NFT marketplace, Swap, and Farming.
- Implement authentication based on IPFS with Moralis for NFT product.
- Handling with DeFi exchange projects using Pancakeswap, Uniswap, Sushiswap and More.
- DEX and Centralized Crypto Exchange, Yield Farming, Liquidity Mining Protocols.
- Using the solidity framework features, optimized the smart contract program and boosted performance by 20%.
- Smart Green Bonds includes an ecological state protocol that connects IoT off-chain data to Smart Contracts on Ethereum.

NOV 2018 - JAN 2020

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER, CLAVAX TECHNOLOGIES LLC

- Implemented pixel perfect frontend by design of client.
- Built websites using React & Django.
- 3d animation effect websites using Three.js and WebGL.
- Implemented SEO (Search Engine Optimization) to existing websites.
- Retrieved data from multiple, different storage APIs, using GraphQL,
- Payment Integration.
- Implemented Chat bot integration to several websites.

- Completed Online game using Unity and Node.js and Websocket.
- Made online game (Poker) using Laravel Livewire and Vue.js.
- Web Hosting to AWS / Cpanel.
- Built Websites using React, Redux, Django, DynamoDB.
- Used ASP.NET Core and Python Flask and Java. Developed an internal application that tracked the life of an order through a windows service and MongoDB.
- Used GraphQL and REST API
- Development of Electron App and Used Next.js and Nuxt.js
- Web Hosting to AWS / Azure.

JUN 2016 - NOV 2018

UNITY DEVELOPER, PERBLUE

- I learned Unity and shader and developed simple game of ketchapp (Spiral).
- Made online game (Aim Lab)

FEB 2013 - JUN 2016

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER, KYNDRYL

- Developed automated software which manages infrastructure without human intervention.
- Built multiple language website using Laravel with Vue is frontend developer.
- Built shopping website using Django with React.
- Implemented SEO(Search Engine Optimization) for several websites.
- Paypal integration using Laravel and Node.js. Web Scrapping using Python.
- Web Hosting to Azure / CWP.

FEB 2011 - JUN 2013

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER INTERN, KYNDRYL

- Implemented Single Page Application architecture and client side MVC using AngularJS.
- Used Bootstrap features such as Model objects, Tabs, Tooltips, Carousals throughout the application.
- Used Angular UI Grid directives such as filters, rootscope, childscope, modal, and template, etc.
- Implemented components and wire-frames using cross-browser compatible CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and Ajax, Angular JS.
- Used ng-view directive to refresh only certain section of the page and reduce the load on the web server.
- Implemented websites suing Laravel Blade and Bootstrap and JavaScript and CSS.

EDUCATION

2008 - 2011

SHANGHAI JIAO TONG UNIVERSITY

BARCHELO OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

I entered the University in 2010, and my major was computer engineering. I studied very hardly so when I graduate the university, I was awarded Bachelor of Computer Engineering.

SKILLS

- Programming Language: C, C++, C#, Javascript, TypeScript, PHP, Python, HTML/CSS, SQL
- Frontend skills: React, Vue, Next, Angular, Svelte
- Backend skills: Node, Express, Laravel, Django, GraphQL
- DBMS: MySQL, MsSQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- VCS: Github
- Game skills: Unity

LANGUAGE

- English: Fluent
- Chinese: Native and Bilingual

CERTIFICATION

- HackerRank (December 24, 2021)
 - 1. C/C++ certification
 - 2. Python certification
 - 3. Node (Javascript) certification
 - 4. React Certification